{
    "id": "fa592942ac594e12b19c25ffce64d40d",
    "title": "Adverbs Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Although she works ……………………, she does not earn enough.",
            "description": "Hard is the adverb for this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "86dc2d743dd642db857f970716be5b42"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ……………………….. happy to hear this.",
            "description": "Very is used without much before adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b2eb258b93644ed58f39282e4ff69f2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………………. rained this month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7dcdb36b9ff74f4b9615460dde009004"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to go into …………………….. about how I managed to do this.",
            "description": "In detail means thoroughly or in depth.",
            "answers": [
                "detail",
                "details"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebdfced4362846a19c858b812423a7af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai can be ……………………… hot in May.",
            "description": "Either could be used here. Too can be used to show negative extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "197dbb93bece45fc9ca9d386ef848d00"
        },
        {
            "question": "A soldier should never behave ……………………..",
            "description": "Cowardly is an adjective. The adverb for this meaning is 'in a cowardly manner'. ",
            "answers": [
                "cowardly",
                "like a coward",
                "in a cowardly manner"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9bef344405bc4c56b291d03f491bdd9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel …………………………….. about his health.",
            "description": "Feel is a copular verb. It is modified by an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "anxiously"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "359d3c294ee24d20ba3dc2c4e132eabd"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ……………………….. injured in the crash.",
            "description": "Badly and fatally are adverbs modifying verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "badly",
                "fatally",
                "deadly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27e9d454e64e475b96d1b6ca764c4082"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ………………………………. with my dogs.",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9335d2bbe7d457f99052021342221e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she ran ………………………., she could not win the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c856d7c4993a454f9a8877ccf80dd85b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was ………………………….. boring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite",
                "too",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "3501f85acf1845a4ba2b227b7c9bfb7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Read the instructions …………………………..",
            "description": "Carefully is the adverb used to modify the verb read. ",
            "answers": [
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12f1b7cab9704d69b7717fff1cb41909"
        }
    ]
}